<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>QuestInLanka Tours</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on QuestInLanka Tours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>8-Days Tea Country To Down South</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8days/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a more detailed itinerary for your 8-days 7 Nights luxury tour package that includes lovely dinners, beach functions, whale watching, safari, Hiking and boat riding:
Day 1: Arrival in Colombo &amp;amp; Way to Kandy Private airport transfer to the hotel Welcome dinner at a fine dining restaurant Nightlife exploration Day 2: Kandy Visit Temple of Tooth Relic Watch a cultural dance performance Peradeniya Botanical Garden Dinner at a rooftop restaurant Day 3: Nuwara Eliya Visit a tea plantation and factory Visit Horton Plains National Park Gregory Lake boat ride Romantic dinner at the hotel Day 4: Ella to Yala Visit Little Adam’s Peak Visit Nine Arches Bridge Scenic train ride through the mountains Dinner at a local restaurant Day 5: Mirissa Whale watching tour Beach activities Dinner at a beachfront restaurant Day 6: Bentota Water sports activities Boat ride in Bentota River Beach party with live music Day 7: Negombo City Tour Visit the Fish Market Boat tour in Muthurajawela Lagoon Beach party with live music Day 8: Departure Transfer to the airport Includes: English Speaking Chauffeur Drivers Air-conditioned Private Tourist Vehicle Special Guide service when required Excludes: Lunch and Dinner Activity charges Sightseeing &amp;amp; entrance fee Flights Visa fees Personal expenses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9-Days Best of Island</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/9days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/9days/</guid>
      <description>Great! Creating a 9-day family tour package that includes ancient cities, wildlife activities, safari, whale watching, and beaches sounds like an exciting adventure for travelers visiting Sri Lanka. Here&amp;rsquo;s a possible itinerary for your tour package.
Day 1: Arrival in Colombo Private airport transfer to the hotel Welcome dinner at a local restaurant Nightlife exploration Day 2: Dambulla and Sigiriya Tour Climb Sigiriya Rock Fortress Visit Dambulla Cave Temple Village tour in Habarana Traditional Sri Lankan dinner with a local family Day 3: Kandy City Tour Visit Temple of Tooth Relic Watch a cultural dance performance Kandy city tour Dinner at a rooftop restaurant Day 4: Nuwara Eliya City Tour Visit a tea plantation and factory Visit Horton Plains National Park Gregory Lake boat ride Romantic dinner at the hotel Day 5: Ella City Tour Visit Little Adam&amp;rsquo;s Peak Visit Nine Arches Bridge Scenic train ride through the mountains Dinner at a local restaurant Day 6: Yala Safari Safari in Yala National Park Beach party with live music Day 7: Mirissa Beach Tour Whale watching tour Beach activities Dinner at a beachfront restaurant Day 8: Negombo City Tour Visit the Fish Market Boat tour in Muthurajawela Lagoon Beach party with live music Day 9: Departure Transfer to the airport Includes: English Speaking Chauffeur Drivers Air-conditioned Private Tourist Vehicle Special Guide service when required Excludes: Lunch and Dinner Activity charges Sightseeing &amp;amp; entrance fee Flights Visa fees Personal expenses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15-Days Sri Lanka Highlights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/15days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/15days/</guid>
      <description>Great! Here&amp;rsquo;s a more detailed itinerary for your 15-day classic tour package that includes lovely dinners, beach functions, whale watching, safari, village tours, and boat riding.
Day 1: Arrival in Colombo Private airport transfer to the hotel Welcome dinner at a local restaurant Nightlife exploration Day 2: Negombo City Tour Visit the Fish Market Boat tour in Muthurajawela Lagoon Beach party with live music Day 3: Anuradhapura Tour Visit ancient temples and ruins in Anuradhapura Traditional Sri Lankan dinner with a local family Day 4: Polonnaruwa and Sigiriya Tour Visit the ancient city of Polonnaruwa Climb Sigiriya Rock Fortress Village tour in Habarana Traditional Sri Lankan dinner with a local family Day 5: Kandy City Tour Visit Temple of Tooth Relic Watch a cultural dance performance Kandy city tour Dinner at a rooftop restaurant Day 6: Nuwara Eliya City Tour Visit a tea plantation and factory Visit Horton Plains National Park Gregory Lake boat ride Romantic dinner at the hotel Day 7: Ella City Tour Visit Little Adam&amp;rsquo;s Peak Visit Nine Arches Bridge Scenic train ride through the mountains Dinner at a local restaurant Day 8: Yala Safari Safari in Yala National Park Beach party with live music Day 9: Mirissa Beach Tour Whale watching tour Beach activities Dinner at a beachfront restaurant Day 10: Galle City Tour Visit Galle Fort Visit Jungle Beach Traditional Sri Lankan dinner with a local family Day 11-12: Bentota Beach Tour Water sports activities Boat ride in Bentota River Beach party with live music Day 13-14: Colombo City Tour Visit Gangaramaya Temple Visit Independence Square Visit Galle Face Green Visit Colombo National Museum Dinner at a local restaurant Day 15: Departure Transfer to the airport Includes: English Speaking Chauffeur Drivers Air-conditioned Private Tourist Vehicle Special Guide service when required Excludes: Lunch and Dinner Activity charges Sightseeing &amp;amp; entrance fee Flights Visa fees Personal expenses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ella Day Tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/day_tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/day_tour/</guid>
      <description>Embark on a Captivating Journey with our Ella Day Tour Package! Immerse yourself in the natural wonders and cultural heritage of this breathtaking hill country destination.
First, we&amp;rsquo;ll take you to the mesmerizing Rawana Falls, where you can witness the sheer beauty and power of this magnificent waterfall. Feel the mist on your face and capture stunning photos of this natural wonder.
Next, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the mystical Rawana Cave Temple, a sacred site filled with rich history and fascinating legends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11-Days Adventure Package</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/11days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/11days/</guid>
      <description>Great! Here&amp;rsquo;s a more detailed itinerary for your 11-day adventure tour package that includes lovely dinners, beach functions, whale watching, safari, village tours, and boat riding.
Day 1: Arrival in Colombo Private airport transfer to the hotel Welcome dinner at a local restaurant Nightlife exploration Day 2: Negombo City Tour Visit the Fish Market Boat tour in Muthurajawela Lagoon Beach party with live music Day 3: Dambulla and Sigiriya Tour Climb Sigiriya Rock Fortress Visit Dambulla Cave Temple Village tour in Habarana Traditional Sri Lankan dinner with a local family Day 4: Kandy City Tour Visit Temple of Tooth Relic Watch a cultural dance performance Kandy city tour Dinner at a rooftop restaurant Day 5: Nuwara Eliya City Tour Visit a tea plantation and factory Visit Horton Plains National Park Gregory Lake boat ride Romantic dinner at the hotel Day 6: Ella City Tour Visit Little Adam&amp;rsquo;s Peak Visit Nine Arches Bridge Scenic train ride through the mountains Dinner at a local restaurant Day 7: Yala Safari Safari in Yala National Park Beach party with live music Day 8: Mirissa Beach Tour Whale watching tour Beach activities Dinner at a beachfront restaurant Day 9: Galle City Tour Visit Galle Fort Visit Jungle Beach Traditional Sri Lankan dinner with a local family Day 10: Bentota Beach Tour Water sports activities Boat ride in Bentota River Beach party with live music Day 11: Departure Transfer to the airport Includes: English Speaking Chauffeur Drivers Air-conditioned Private Tourist Vehicle Special Guide service when required Excludes: Lunch and Dinner Activity charges Sightseeing &amp;amp; entrance fee Flights Visa fees Personal expenses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9-Days Lovers Special</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/9days_hm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/9days_hm/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations on your upcoming honeymoon! QuestinLanka is thrilled to offer you a 9-day honeymoon tour package that will make your trip unforgettable with romantic and lovely experiences.
Day 1: Colombo Arrival in Colombo Upon arrival at the airport, our representative will greet you and transfer you to your hotel in Colombo. You can relax and enjoy the evening at your leisure. Day 2-3 Dambulla Visit the ancient city of Polonnaruwa Sigiriya rock fortress Dambulla Cave Temple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/activities/</guid>
      <description>Heritage of sri lanka Sri Lanka is a land of ancient civilization, where the echoes of a rich cultural heritage can still be heard. The island boasts a multitude of cultural and heritage sites that bear testament to the island&amp;rsquo;s history and diversity. From the ancient kingdoms to colonial-era forts, Sri Lanka is home to an array of architectural marvels that will leave visitors in awe.
Anuradhapura, the ancient capital of Sri Lanka, is home to an array of ruins that offer a glimpse into the country&amp;rsquo;s rich history.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
